<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A slum blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A slum blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial part 1: Getting started</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The aim of slumdown is to provide a simple Hugo template suitable for R users who want to build a website or start a blog, and is designed to be compatible with both blogdown and hugodown. In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to get started. The assumed reader for this tutorial is an R user who has some experience with R Markdown, but is unfamiliar with blogdown, hugodown, or Hugo itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial part 2: Customising posts</title>
      <link>/post/customising-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/customising-posts/</guid>
      <description>In general I want to use a consistent palette and header across a site, but there are occasions where I might want a single page to use a different style. I don’t want to have to edit with low level settings to do that. In the second part of the tutorial I discuss this kind of customisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial part 3: Deploying the site</title>
      <link>/post/deploying-the-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/deploying-the-site/</guid>
      <description>The usual advice for deploying a blogdown or hugodown site is to deploy to Netlify rather than GitHub Pages, because there are a few peculiarities to GitHub Pages that can make it difficult. The third part of the tutorial walks you through both versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A project of one&#39;s own</title>
      <link>/project/of-ones-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 1929 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/of-ones-own/</guid>
      <description>An example of a project page, creating a simple generative art system in R. There is more code on this page than elsewhere on the example site, which may be useful if you want to see what the syntax highlighting looks like for slumdown sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About the author Danielle Navarro is a computational cognitive scientist and Associate Professor at the University of New South Wales. Her research focuses on human reasoning and statistical methods in the behavioural sciences. On occasions she has been known to masquerade as a part-time statistician, data scientist and an unskilled software developer. She is also a devoted R-Lady, an aspiring generative artist, and at times a general purpose nuisance. She is prone to describing herself in the third person in biographies, but is willing to admit that it&amp;rsquo;s super weird.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>